<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Assignments :: AD3 Homepage</title><link>https://ad3-uu-se.github.io/assignments/index.html</link><description>Help, Solution, and Grading Sessions and Guide for the Perplexed.
The course has 2 mandatory assignments, to be done in teams of two. The assignments are worth 2 higher-education credits (ECTS credits) in total.
Help Sessions, Each assignment has 3 timetabled help sessions. Help sessions are the only time that you can help from the assistants. We will not give support at other times.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-uk</language><managingEditor>justin.pearson@it.uu.se (Justin Pearson)</managingEditor><webMaster>justin.pearson@it.uu.se (Justin Pearson)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:03:35 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ad3-uu-se.github.io/assignments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assignment 1</title><link>https://ad3-uu-se.github.io/assignments/assignment1/index.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:03:35 +0100</pubDate><author>justin.pearson@it.uu.se (Justin Pearson)</author><guid>https://ad3-uu-se.github.io/assignments/assignment1/index.html</guid><description>Source files for the assignment The assignment instructions, and zip file providing all the necessary files.
Software Resources Problem 1 (Assignment 1): Effortless and free access to MIP solvers is provided by the NEOS Server for Optimisation (search for “mixed integer linear programming”). We then recommend you use the world-class commercial MIP solver Gurobi Optimizer (or, but only in case of a temporary licensing issue with Gurobi at NEOS, the open-source MIP solver HiGHS), via the AMPL modelling language: when using the NEOS server, you do not need to install the AMPL integrated development environment (IDE) or AMPL command-line interface (CLI) or a MIP solver. Use a commands file with option gurobi_options 'outlev=1'; solve; # Write display commands here: display ___; in order to turn on verbose printing, which includes the optimality gap.</description></item></channel></rss>